Ahmed Ragab

Jenior Front-end

CONTACT

+20-12-2831-7491

ahmedkavo17@gmail.com

www.ahmedragab24

https://github.com

EDUCATION

Faculty of Social Work

Study of Social Sciences and Psychology (2019-2024)

ABOUT ME

I am a front-end website programmer who specializes in converting designs into interactive web pages. I strive to achieve an excellent user experience and provide a smooth and comfortable browsing experience for users. I have experience with major programming languages and popular frameworks, and pay great attention to interoperability and performance optimization. You work effectively within development teams and communicate well with customers and colleagues.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

(2020 - 2023)

 I worked on many projects through freelance sites such as Up Work mostaql

Jenior Front-end

(2022-2023)

 I worked with Saudi Orkend Company as a remote front-end web developer

SKILLS

- Hrml Css Javascript Typescript
- Bootstrap Tailwind Sass
- React Redux Toolkit Next.js
- Oop Algorithms Data structure
- Git & Github

MY PROJECTS

- Watches Website
- Car Website
- Real estate website
- maritime agencies
- Pharmacist portfolio